The best way to start a speech and the way that I hope all of you use from now forward
is the same way we start a story to a child.
But in business, you don't hear Jack Welsh saying once upon a time.
Steve Jobs doesn't start his speeches once upon a time.
So there's a grown-up way of saying once upon a time.
The way you tell stories as an adult is in October, it was the last time I was in this
room, there were 120 people in the room and I was having a little conversation with one
of the world experts on public speaking.
And he said something to me that's had me thinking ever since.
He said something to me that changed what I think about what's important in speaking.
Now I can pause for about 30 seconds, two, three minutes.
And you want to know what he said.